https://www.wirespring.com/privacy.html

(800) 989-9269         Customer Login
Menu
HomeIndustries Smart Devices (M2M / IoT)Digital SignageLED BillboardsInteractive KiosksBanks and Credit UnionsCorporate CommunicationsEducationHealthcareHotelsRestaurant Menu BoardsRetail and CPGTransit and TransportationProducts FireCast ClientCenter CloudFireCast ClientCenter Virtual ServerFireCast OSFireCast Display CoreFireCast EasyStartFireCast SmartFlowPricingSupport Contact Tech SupportBlogs Digital Signage InsiderM2M InsiderCompany About UsManagement TeamCustomer TestimonialsCareersContact
Privacy Policy
Last updated: November 3, 2020
WireSpring is committed to protecting the privacy of your information. This privacy policy outlines the steps we take to protect your privacy on our corporate Homepages (located at wirespring.com and simpledigitalsignage.com), on FireCast ClientCenter (located at wirespring.net), and on the FireCast SmartFlow queuing interface (located at queu.net).
Organization Providing This Privacy Policy
WireSpring is the organization providing this privacy policy, and is also the organization collecting information in accordance with it. Our contact information is as follows:
WireSpring Technologies, Inc.2900 West Cypress Creek Road, Suite 15Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309 USAprivacy@wirespring.com
Information Collection and Use
WireSpring is the sole owner of the information collected on our websites, although you remain the owner of any Private Data and Billing Information on FireCast ClientCenter (as defined below). We do not sell or rent this information to third-parties. However, we ourselves may use this information in the manner described in this privacy policy.
Depending on the extent of your relationship with WireSpring, the information contained in our database may vary. For instance, if you simply browse our sites without contacting us via a form or live chat, the info may simply consist of the pages you have viewed on our sites. Conversely, if you choose to fill out a form in order to receive product information via email, open the corresponding email, and choose to participate in a live chat session, the info in our database may also include a record of those interactions.
Our websites are directed to a general audience, and are not directed to children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our database.
Required Disclosures
Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web sites. We intend to cooperate with all law enforcement authorities seeking data in pursuit of any or all suspected terrorist activities.
Security
WireSpring takes reasonable precautions under current technology to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information (including Billing Information and/or Private Data on ClientCenter) we attempt to protect this information, both online and offline, with the same methods that we use to protect our own proprietary data. ClientCenter session data is protected using 256-bit SSL encryption.
Cookies
Our cookie policy may be found at https://www.wirespring.com/cookies.html.
Usage Tracking and Log Files
When you view our sites and open certain emails from us, we collect the following information:
- IP address - Demographic data (such as your web browser, operating system, and time zone) - Pages you have viewed on our sites - Details about how you reached our sites (such as the link you clicked on or the keywords you entered on a search engine) - Details on which emails from us you have opened or taken action on
Forms
Our websites may include various forms for you to fill out. For instance, we may ask you to fill out a form in order to receive product information via email. The decision to fill out these forms is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice of whether or not to disclose this information. The information we request may include contact information (such as your name and email address) and form-specific information (such as the products you are interested in). We use this information to provide the requested services to you, as well as to improve our products and services.
Your contact information will only be used internally, and we do not sell or rent this information to third-parties. However, if you utilize our LED Billboard Cost Estimator tool and enter your contact information into the tool, we may share your contact info and the other information you entered with a small group of trusted referral partners. These referral partners may then contact you to provide you with a pricing quote for the LED billboard configuration that you are interested in. If you ultimately decide to purchase an LED billboard from one of our partners, we may receive a referral fee from the partner.
Live Chat
If you choose to participate in a live chat session, we may retain copies of the chat session transcript for use in improving our products and services or for other customer support purposes. As detailed above, we may also use cookies to store certain information that allows us to identify you upon subsequent chat sessions or visits to our sites.
Comments and User Forums
Our Homepages may provide you with the ability to leave comments on blog articles, and ClientCenter includes a user forum that you may utilize to post questions and answer questions submitted by other users. For comments, you control the name that is displayed alongside the comment text. For forum posts, your user identifier is generated automatically, and is intended to provide a reasonable level of anonymity. However, please be aware that anything you post in a comment or in a forum post will be visible to others. So, you should not use comments or forum posts to share any information that is private or sensitive in nature.
Private Data
Private Data includes any files that you upload and store on ClientCenter, as well as other data (such as advertising statistics) obtained by you during your regular use of ClientCenter. We will not sell or rent any Private Data that identifies you to third parties. However, when requested by you we may access your Private Data to provide technical support or customer service.
Billing Information
If you are a paying customer (such as a ClientCenter subscriber), we may provide information including your name, address, and credit card number to trusted organizations (such as credit card processing services) to ensure that we receive proper payment for our products and services. If you elect to purchase products or services from WireSpring channel partners or contractors, we may provide these organizations with the corresponding billing and contact information to enable them to provide service and support to you. Should the need to collect any delinquent fees owed to us arise, we reserve the right to provide billing information to a third-party collection agency.
We may offer the option for you to purchase our products and services directly from our websites. If you choose to utilize this online ordering functionality, information including your name, address, and the products you are purchasing will typically be made available to both WireSpring and our trusted e-commerce partners, such as FoxyCart. However, your credit card information will only be known to the specific payment processing firm who collected it from you, such as Amazon Pay. Since your credit card information is not made available to WireSpring, we do not share it with third-parties.
Links
Our sites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by our sites.
Services Provided by Third Parties
We contract with third-parties to provide certain services on our sites, including the following:
- Web analytics - Live chat - Email delivery - Online ordering - Embedded video playback - Site search - SMS messaging
To the best of our knowledge, these firms are committed to protecting the privacy of any information that they collect about you on our behalf. However, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of outside firms.
We use Clicky for web analytics on our Homepages. Pursuant to the Clicky Terms of Service, we are providing the following disclosure: "We use Clicky to log and analyze the traffic to our web site. You may review Clicky's privacy policy at https://clicky.com/terms/privacy. A "Unique ID" tracking cookie is used for the "legitimate purpose" of identifying unique visitors, but otherwise no "personal data" is logged."
We may use Google Analytics for web analytics on our Homepages. Our use of Google Analytics may include Google Analytics Advertising Features, such as remarketing. This feature enables us to show you ads for our products while you browse the web. For example, if you visit our site and subsequently visit a third-party site that displays certain types of advertising from Google, you may see ads for our products on that site. To control the information Google uses to show you ads, please visit https://adssettings.google.com. To learn more about how Google uses information from sites or apps that use its services, please visit https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites.
We also provide social sharing buttons to make it easier for you to share certain content from our websites via social networking sites. Use of these sharing buttons is subject to the privacy policies of the corresponding social networking sites.
Customer Service and Service Announcements
We communicate with you on a regular basis to provide requested services. If you submit questions or comments about your account, we will reply via email or phone, as appropriate. Occasionally, it may be necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if access to ClientCenter is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications.
For Consumers Who Use the FireCast SmartFlow Queuing System at a Participating Venue
WireSpring does not store any personal information acquired from consumers who use its FireCast SmartFlow Queuing System for queuing at participating venues, except for a phone number or other identifier for a queuing session that is used to facilitate the queuing service. WireSpring will not send any communications to consumers except during the queueing session and provides an opt-out option for consumers who do not want to receive updates during the queueing session. WireSpring requires participating venues that offer the FireCast SmartFlow Queuing System to obtain a separate consent from consumers before sending any communications to consumers outside the queueing session.
Privacy Settings and Opt-Out
To review or update your email subscriptions, please visit https://www.wirespring.com/forms/manage-your-subscriptions. You may also opt-out of an email subscription by clicking the opt-out link that accompanies the email.
To review or update your cookie consent settings, please visit https://www.wirespring.com/cookies.html.
Updating, Deleting, or Requesting a Copy of Your Information
Routine updates to your personal information may be made using the tools described in the section above. If you would like to make other updates, or wish to delete your personal information on file with us or request a copy of that information, please contact us at privacy@wirespring.com.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update this privacy policy from time to time, and you may find a link to the most current version at the bottom of our Homepages and on the ClientCenter login page.
Questions About This Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@wirespring.com.
Questions?
Get pricing  •
Call us at (800) 989-9269 or +1 (954) 548-3300  •
Chat with us online
Copyright © 2020 WireSpring Technologies, Inc. All rights reserved.
Site Map • Privacy • Cookies • Syndication • Legal
HomeIndustries Smart Devices (M2M / IoT)Digital SignageLED BillboardsInteractive KiosksBanks and Credit UnionsCorporate CommunicationsEducationHealthcareHotelsRestaurant Menu BoardsRetail and CPGTransit and TransportationProducts FireCast ClientCenter CloudFireCast ClientCenter Virtual ServerFireCast OSFireCast Display CoreFireCast EasyStartFireCast SmartFlowPricingSupport Contact Tech SupportBlogs Digital Signage InsiderM2M InsiderCompany About UsManagement TeamCustomer TestimonialsCareersContact
